Excuse me, miss.
I've received a call about loitering.
There's no one here, idiot.
Oh, yeah.
What's up?
I need information.
Who had Big Joe nicked?
Arresting officer was George Brightwell,
I think.
No, I'm sure.
Danny, you forgetting you owe me a grand?
I'm not talking about the arresting officer.
I'm saying who made the call?
I'm not totally sure about this,
but I think it's Callum Miller.
Detective Sergeant, right?
What do you know about him?
He's Michael Eversholt's crony in chief.
Beyond that, I'd be guessing.
But I know someone who knows more.
You need to talk to Curtis Watson,
detective Constable.
Hates Miller.
I don't blame him. Give me his details.
You may be looking at the crews and
thinking we're the dominant power
in Croydon.
In reality, we're small fry.
Top of the food chain in the borough
is Croydon East MP Stuart Jordan,
a corrupt piece of shit who views
the borough treasury as his
personal
piggy bank.
And just further down is Police Borough
Commander Michael Eversholt.
You Watson?
Call me Curtis.
You know Callum Miller?
Bit of a history lesson.
Michael Eversholt gets transferred
from Eltham to
Croton in nineteen
ninety-nine
in the wake of the Stephen Lawrence inquiry.
Institutional racism.
And for all we can tell,
he's got no plans to improve once he
gets to Croton.
Then he makes borough commander,
and everything gets worse.
Then a few months back,
I make a mistake.
I start asking questions.
Questions like why it took me twice
as long to make detective.
Why one of the black PCs found a banana
in his locker.
Eversholt doesn't go after me directly.
He uses his lackey, Miller,
to drive me out. Bogus leads,
interviews with dead-end witnesses.
Even now
I'm working on a case of a few dead cats
that everyone knows are just foxes.
Do you know why Miller wanted Big Joe
Adebayor?
To go down?
No. But if we find out why,
we can push for a malicious prosecution
angle.
Your boy goes free,
and Miller is left red-faced.
Where do I start?
He's got a safe in his office he puts
the most sensitive case files in.
The truth will be in there.
I made a copy of the key a while back.
I wanted to nail him. This might be it.
I can give you a five-minute window,
but if you get caught,
your life is over.
You wanna nominate someone for this?
Nah. Handle this myself in it